[{"answer": " Hi Ned.  Im Nancy Grey, one of the career counselors here at the school.  It", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Its nice to meet you too.  Im doing well, thank you", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Hi Ned.  Im Nancy Grey, one of the career counselors here at the school.  It", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " So what brings you to our office today, Ned", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Its nice to meet you too.  Im doing well, thank you", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Well, in two weeks Im going to graduate and I still dont have a job lined up", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 20, "question": " So what brings you to our office today, Ned", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " I see.  What is your degree in", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Well, in two weeks Im going to graduate and I still dont have a job lined up", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Business", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 25, "question": " I see.  What is your degree in", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " OK, good.  That is a very desirable major to employers.  So tell me, what step", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Business", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Umm, Ive looked in the classified ads in the newspaper and looked a", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 30, "question": " OK, good.  That is a very desirable major to employers.  So tell me, what step", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Those are good places to start.  Did you apply for any jobs that you saw", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Umm, Ive looked in the classified ads in the newspaper and looked a", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " I applied to about five, but I didnt hear anything back from the companies", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Those are good places to start.  Did you apply for any jobs that you saw", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Well, dont get discouraged.  It takes time to find a job.  Today I can give yo", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 38, "question": " I applied to about five, but I didnt hear anything back from the companies", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Thank you.  I really need some help", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Well, dont get discouraged.  It takes time to find a job.  Today I can give yo", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Now, have you tried any networking to meet potential employers and ge", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Thank you.  I really need some help", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " To be honest, Ive heard the word networking a lot, but Im not quite sure what i", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Now, have you tried any networking to meet potential employers and ge", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": "Networking is basically a way to make connections with other people and buil", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 50, "question": " To be honest, Ive heard the word networking a lot, but Im not quite sure what i", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " OK, I understand.  No, I definitely havent done any of that.  Where would I start", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Networking is basically a way to make connections with other people and buil", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": "The first thing you want to do is tell everyone you know  friends, family", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 55, "question": " OK, I understand.  No, I definitely havent done any of that.  Where would I start", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Do you know of any business organizations in this area", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 63, "question": "The first thing you want to do is tell everyone you know  friends, family", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " There are quite a few.  At the end of our meeting today, I can give you a list o", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Do you know of any business organizations in this area", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " That would be great", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 68, "question": " There are quite a few.  At the end of our meeting today, I can give you a list o", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Another great networking tool is right here on campus  your professors, othe", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 69, "question": " That would be great", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " You know, I never even thought about talking to my professors or other student", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Another great networking tool is right here on campus  your professors, othe", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Talking with many different people is always a great way to get information an", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 84, "question": " You know, I never even thought about talking to my professors or other student", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Do most people find jobs through networking", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Talking with many different people is always a great way to get information an", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Many do.  In fact, only about 30% of available jobs are advertised.  The othe", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Do most people find jobs through networking", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " It seems that way", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Many do.  In fact, only about 30% of available jobs are advertised.  The othe", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " So do you have any questions about the networking process", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 94, "question": " It seems that way", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " No, I dont think so", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 95, "question": " So do you have any questions about the networking process", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Heres what I want you to do.  I want you to start talking to as many people yo", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 96, "question": " No, I dont think so", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " That sounds great!  Im definitely excited about this networking thing.  Without it", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 102, "question": " Heres what I want you to do.  I want you to start talking to as many people yo", "qSentId": 101},{"answer": " Definitely.  So just give our office a call in about two weeks and schedul", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 106, "question": " That sounds great!  Im definitely excited about this networking thing.  Without it", "qSentId": 105},{"answer": " OK, I will", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 110, "question": " Definitely.  So just give our office a call in about two weeks and schedul", "qSentId": 109},{"answer": " It has been very nice talking with you today and if you have any question", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 111, "question": " OK, I will", "qSentId": 110},{"answer": " OK.  Thank you so much!  Bye", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 115, "question": " It has been very nice talking with you today and if you have any question", "qSentId": 114},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "01-08", "aSentId": 116, "question": " OK.  Thank you so much!  Bye", "qSentId": 115}]
